Experienced cloud infrastructure and support engineer with varied and proven capabilities across network configuration, maintenance, automation and security. Thorough, meticulous and adaptive, I thrive in high-pressure environments and relish the opportunity to demonstrate and build upon my extensive skills set.

Technical Proficiencies

	CLOUD INFRASTRUCTURE	Azure IaaS, ARM, NSG, Express Route, Public and Private Peering, Vnet and Subnet, Json templates, UDR's, MFA, Enterprise Portal, RBAC, Resource Groups, Disaster Recovery, Azure Recovery Services, Availability Sets, Managed Disks and Storage accounts, Azure Lift and shift migration, CloudDyn, Office365, InTune, EMS, Exchange Online, Skype for Business, Serverless, terraform, Kubernetes, PaaS	
	NETWORKING	Wireless Access Point Maintenance, DHCP, DNS, WAN, VPN, RSA and TCP/IP Configuration, SonicWall Firewall, Cisco ASA, Meraki MX, RSA, IPV6 (Direct Access) HP ProCurve switching, vLANs & Subnetting, 7 layer OSI Model, iPerf	

CAREER HISTORY

Redington Ltd [May 2018 – Present]

VP Cloud Infrastructure Engineer [Jan 2019 – Present]

- Cloud migration from on premise to Azure
- Team City and Octopus Deploy for CI/CD
- Migration away from traditional infrastructure solutions to laaS e.g SQL MI DRaaS
- Architecture, configuration & maintenance of network infrastructure (Meraki)
- Serverless deployment for both Azure & AWS
- Kubernetes to manage docker deployments in Azure
- Design and Implementation of cost saving initiatives across cloud platforms
- End-to-end deployment of remote working solution
- Technical lead in obtaining ISO 27001 Accreditation
- Processing Subject Access requests in line with GDPR
- Key technical point of contact for all members of the technology team inclusive of CTO, head of development and head of delivery and support (DevOps)

Associate Cloud Infrastructure Engineer [May 2018 – December 2018]

- AWS architecture, configuration & implementation for our in-house development team
- Powershell automation for IT department & Business efficiency gains
- Management & configuration of HA firewall cluster (Checkpoint) on premise and deployment of firewalls in Azure
- IDS management (Darktrace)
- Responsible for regular penetration tests on infrastructure (Nessus, Burpsuite)
- Sophos AV Management
- Citrix XenApp and Netscaler configuration and maintenance
- Certificate Management (SSL/ADFS/THAWTE)

ION Group Infrastructure Engineer [June 2017 – May 2018]

 Managing, configuring and upgrading Active Directory i.e. domain controller upgrade, domain functional level upgrade, forest functional level upgrade, domain/forest consolidation & decommissioning, user migrations between forests and domains

- Administering Active Directory and GPO's (multi-site, multi forest environment), with strong knowledge of Group Policies
- Windows 10 Rollout (SCCM/MDT)
- Support of Linux (CentOS 6/7 and Ubuntu) operating systems
- MySQL/Postgres SQL
- Office 365 Administration
- VMware/VSphere
- Working with Server, Desktop, Network and Telephony providers
- Building an Infrastructure rack end to end, including UPS, Switch configuration, patching, Server build (physical and via SCCM 2012)
- Configuring switches, routers and firewalls (Cisco)

M&C Saatchi 2nd Line Engineer [March 2015 – June 2017]

- Configuring HP Pro Curve Switches (2910's and 2920's)
- Monitoring Nagios (Infrastructure Monitoring Application) and resolving issues found
- Managing our estates Anti-Virus application (Kaspersky)
- Cloud Service administration (Egnyte Cent0S4.5 [Linux] hybrid cloud solution)
- Set up and management of HP/Aruba MSM Wireless Access Points
- Creating and Managing virtual hosts using VMWare
- Server maintenance and support (Windows Server 2003, 2008 R2 and 2012)
- Avaya IP telecom voice and data support
- Development and maintenance of standard desktop images using Windows Deployment Services
- Application packaging and deployment for Mac devices using LANrev
- Technical support; troubleshooting support queries in person, via phone, email and the IT Service Desk system normally as an escalation point from first line

Hewlett Packard Desktop Support Engineer [Jan 2013 – March 2015]

Entry-level managed service provider for contractors including Commerzbank & Deutsche Bank

- Trade Floor Support (Bloomberg, Reuters)
- Hardware maintenance & support (Break/Fix)
- Windows 7 roll out
- Consumables Management: All MFPs + Print Pod Printers
- Update the NAC database
- Management of on-site spares stock

EDUCATION AND PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT

- Rooks Heath High School: 2002-2006
 - GCSE: English, Maths, Science, Media, Business Studies, French, Religious Studies, Citizenship
- Stanmore College: 2006 2008
 - A-Levels: Psychology, Sociology, English Literature and Media Studies
- Westminster University: 2008-2010
 - Diploma in Psychology
- Certifications
 - CCNA Routing and Switching
 - ITIL Foundation
 - ComptTIA Sever+
 - HP2-T25 HP Rack and Tower Server Solutions
 - HP2-T26 HP Servicing HP Bladesystem Solutions